Hi, Hi, Yvonne.
Hi, Hi ,Yvonne.
You didn't have to work late.
你今天居然用不着工作到很晚,
This is a nice surprise.
这可真是一大惊喜啊.
Yes. I'm a free man.
Yes. 我现在是一身轻了.
But it looks like you two are still at it.
不过看样子你们俩还在忙着呢.
No, no, We're all finished.
No, no ,我们已经干完了.
I'm just waiting for Douglas to pick me up.
我只是在等Douglas来接我.
Is your car in the shop again, Yvonne?
你的车又进维修站了吗，Yvonne?
Yes, It's old and cranky and loud enough to wake the dead.
是的. 这部车又旧又破, 声音大得连死人都能吵醒.
I just have to buy a new one.
我是非得买辆新车不可了.
We really do need two cars.
我们也的确需要有两部车.
Well, sure. Douglas must just about live in his;
Well, 那当然. Douglas其实差不多就住在车里了;
you have to in real estate.
不过搞房地产的都得这样.
Right. So I'm stuck either waiting for a ride from someone,
说的是.所以我要么得等着搭别人的车,
or taking cabs.
要么乘出租车.
Then I get to listen to cabbies telling very long,
那样的话，我就得听出租车司机讲很长,
very boring stories. It's very annoying.
很无聊的故事. 真让人心烦.
I don't get annoyed at that.
我就不会觉得烦.
I love talkative cabbies.
我喜欢话多的出租车司机.
Let's trade cars.
那我们换车好了,
You'll get lots of time in cabs.
那样你就会有很多时间坐在出租车里了.
So, how was your day?
So，你今天过得怎么样?
It was a big one.
今天是重大的一天，
I gave my notice.
我交了辞呈.
Well, that certainly makes it real.
Well，那你参加公职竞选的事就定下来了.
Oh, yeah.
You can't run for state office if you're employed by the state.
你不能参加公职竞选, 如果你还在为政府部门工作的话.
Are you going to set up a private practice?
你是不是打算开一家私人律师事务所?
Yep.
There he is. Have a good night.
他来了. 祝你们晚上过得愉快.
So, how do you want to celebrate?
So, 你打算怎么庆祝?
Rent a movie, get a pizza to go?
租一部片子看看, 再去买份比萨带回来吃?
You sure know how to show a girl a good time.
你可真懂得哄女孩子开心.